Tyler Young

Support Communicator and Documentation Writer

Website: tyler-young.com Email: tyler@tyler-young.com Phone: (360) 601-4398 Location: Los Angeles, CA

Customer support expert with 4 years of experience in crafting user-friendly technical instructions for all skills levels. My goal is to be in a technical writing role as part of a team focused on customer success.

Experience

Customer Support Agent

January 2014 – July 2017

Media Temple

- Troubleshot issues with LAMP servers, git databases, website development, email.
- Maintained and updated knowledge base documentation.
- Wrote widely-adopted instructions and scripts for many common customer problems.
- Resolved customer tickets with a customer satisfaction rating of over 95%.
- Trained new team members, assisted other agents with troubleshooting.
- Member of incident management team for outages and customer-facing issues.

Independent Developer

May 2013 – Present

- Developed games using the Unity and GameMaker Studio game engines.
- Created a profitable algorithm for trading currencies on the foreign exchange market.
- Scripted in C#, JavaScript, and Python programming languages.
- Developed launch and marketing plan for independent iOS game (to be launched).

Research Assistant

May 2012 - May 2013

Willamette University

- Conducted studies using student and community-member participants.
- Co-authored published research paper and performed statistical analysis of results.

Education

Bachelor of Arts, Psychology

June 2013

Willamette University College

- Merit Scholarship
- Thesis: The Effectiveness of Educational Video Games in a Classroom Setting

Achievements

Eagle Scout May 2008

Published research paper

August 2013

Dixon, K., Young, T. & Miller, J. (2013, August). The Influence of Selective Attention during Memory Retrieval on Subsequent Memory Performance in Young and Older Adults. Poster session presented at the 35th Annual Conference of the Cognitive Science Society. Berlin, Germany.

Skills

Technical writing, JIRA, C#, JavaScript, Python, Linux, Git, Adobe Creative Suite, Graphic Design, Photography